<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>People on Institute of Smart City &amp; Management</title>
    <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/</link>
    <description>Recent content in People on Institute of Smart City &amp; Management</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2021 by [ISCM](https://iscm.ueh.edu.vn)</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Tu Anh Trinh</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-trinh-tu-anh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-trinh-tu-anh/</guid>
      <description>Courses New urban Economics and city marketing Smart Urban Design StudioLab Urban Management Smart City Road Safety Land-use and Transportation Aviation Operation Academic Doctor of Engineering, Transportation, Hasselt University, Belgium, 2008 -2013 Master of Engineering, Transportation, Asian Institute of Technology, international institution based in Bangkok, Thailand 2001 - 2003 Bachelor of Engineering, Transport - Economics Department, University of Transport and Communication, Vietnam 1996 - 2000 Academic Experiences Director, Institute of Smart City and Management, University of Economics HCMC, May 2020 - Present Head, Planning Department, Ton Duc Thang University, September 2014 - May 2020 Dean, Aviation Faculty, Vietnam Aviation Academy, 2007 – December 2013 Lecturer, University of Transport and Communication, September 2003- 2007 Assistant Lecturer, September 2000 – August 2001 Professional Memberships LENS (Learning Network on Sustainability) WiTL (Woman in Transport Leadership Workshop) RTIRN (Road Traffic Injuries Research Network) UEM Network (Urban Environmental Management Network) EASTS (Eastern Asia Society for Transportation Studies) TSSV (Transportation Studies Society of Vietnam) ISSOT (International Student Network on Transport Research) Click HERE for Publication </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Ducksu Seo</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-ducsu-seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-ducsu-seo/</guid>
      <description>Academic and Research Profile Professor at Handong Global University, South Korea (2019 – Now) Head of NIBC Global Institute, Vietnam (2015-Now) Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Dong-Su Yi</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-dong-su-yi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-dong-su-yi/</guid>
      <description>Academic and Research Profile 2013- 2020 Graduate school of Sejong Univ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M. Arch. Mai Tran</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-maitran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-maitran/</guid>
      <description>Courses Building Construction/Structure Theories of Architectural Design Design Studios International design Studios Urban planning and housing International Experiences Instructor in International design Studios in Thailand (2018), Myanmar (2019), Vietnam (2016, 2017, 2018, 2019, 2020) Lecturer exchange in Hasselt University, Belgium on March, 2018 Member of Women in Transport Leadership (WiTL) Member of Lens </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prof. Rob Cuyvers</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-rob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-rob/</guid>
      <description>Academic and Research Profile Supervisor MAD-research group (2013 – 2020) Supervisor Research Group ArcK (2013 – 2018) President PXL-MAD, School of arts (2013 – 2019) Dean of the Faculty of Architecture and arts (2013 – 2018) President of research group Arck and MAD-research (2004 – 2013) Head of the department of Architecture, Interior architecture and Arts at the University College PHL (2004 – 2013) President of the Media, Arts and Design-faculty (2009 – 2012) Director Research group Mobility and Environment University College PHL (2001 – 2004) Guest lecturer “Hogeschool voor Verkeerskunde” (1999 – 2000) Guest lecturer urban planning at Sint-Lucas Gent (1998) Urban planning at KULeuven (1979) BA Philosophy at KULeuven (1977) Civil engineering at KULeuven (1976) Click HERE for Publication </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Nam Le</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-nam-le/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-nam-le/</guid>
      <description>Courses Urban Resilience and Risk Assessment Data Analytics and Solutions for Architect and Urban Planner Asset Management for Buildings and Engineering Systems System Engineering Project Management Academic and Research Profile Research Associate at Institute of Infrastructure and Construction Management (IBI), Swisss Federal Institute of Technology (ETH Zurich) - (2010-2016) Postdoc Researcher, Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M.Arch. Sandhya Rao</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/sandhya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/sandhya/</guid>
      <description> Courses Basic Studiolab 3 Basic Studiolab 5 Academic and Research Profile Associate Professor, Dayananda Sagar College of Architecture (Jan 2017 - 2022) Co-Founder, Citylab BLR (Aug 2015 - 2020) Key Collaborator India, Citymakers (Barcelona) (Aug 2018 - now) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prof. Chamun Koo</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-chamunkoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-chamunkoo/</guid>
      <description>Academic and Research Profile Director, East-Sea Rim Research Institute of Economy and Culture (2005 – Now) Chief Editor, Hwan Dong Hae Review: Far East Regional Studies (2005 – Now) Director, Urban Environment Project Team, UNESCO UNITWIN, Handong Global (1998 - Now) Professor/Dean, School of Spatial Environment System Engineering, Handong Global University (1995 – Now) Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. To Kien</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-to-kien/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/dr-to-kien/</guid>
      <description>Courses History of Architecture and Urbanism Urban anthropoly: How to fosster civic engagement Architecture StudioLab 2: commercial building Landscape Design StudioLab Smart Urban Design StudioLab Architecture StudioLab 1 Advanced International Urban Development Theory of Urban Structure Academic and Research Profile Adjunct Assistant Professor, Singapore University of Technology and Design (SUTD) (2016-2017) Senior Research Scientist, SUTD (2011-2016) Postdoctoral Research Fellow, Kyushu University (2009 -2011) Guest Associate Professor and Course Coordinator, Kyushu University (2009) Postdoctoral Research Fellow - Guest Scholar, Kumamoto University, Japan (2008) PhD of Architecture, Kumamoto University, Japan (2008) Master of Architecture in Urban Design, Berlin-Weissensee Arts Academy (KHB), Germany (2000) Bachelor of Architecture and Planning, National University of Civil Engineering, Vietnam (1996) International Experiences Senior Planner &amp;amp; Project Manager, Eight-Japan Engineering Consultants Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M.Sc. Hoai Pham</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-hoai-pham/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-hoai-pham/</guid>
      <description>Courses Urban Resilience and Risk Assessment Data Analytics and Solutions for Architect and Urban Planner Asset Management for Buildings and Engineering Systems System Engineering Project Management Academic and Research Profile Doctoral student in Transportation Sciences, Hasselt University (Belgium) (2020-2024) Master of Transportation Sciences, Hasselt University (Belgium) (2017-2019) Bachelor of Business Administration, Vietnam Aviation Academy (2010-2014) International Experiences Viags Tan Son Nhat (2016-2017) Payment officer Hoa Sao Group (2015) Supervisor for Vietjet Air call center Jetstar Pacific Airlines (2014-2015) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B.E. Le Viet</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-le-viet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-le-viet/</guid>
      <description>Academic and Research Profile Bachelor of Engineering, Urban Planning, Ton Duc Thang University(2017) International Experiences ERAMUS+ Exchange in Architecture, Hasselt University, Belgium </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M.Arch. Steven Petit</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/mar-steven/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/mar-steven/</guid>
      <description>Courses Smart and Resilient Landscape Design Landscape Design StudioLab Ecological City Planning in smart urbanism Academic and Research Profile Guest lecturer design / academic staff member at University of Hasselt, Belgium (2018 – 2020) MA Urban Design and Spatial Planning at KU Leuven, Belgium (2007) BA after BA Landscape Development at University College Ghent – KASK, Belgium (2004) BA Garden and Landscape Architecture at University College Ghent – KASK, Belgium (2003) International Experiences Design office OMGEVING</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M.Sc. Tam Do</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-tam-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-tam-do/</guid>
      <description>Courses Theories of Architectural Design Smart and Resilient Landscape Design Smart Urban Design New Urban Economics and City Marketing Urban Planning Studiolab Architecture Academic and Research Profile Collaborator in Research at Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM-UEH) Master of Science in Sustainable Urban Development at Vietnamese Germane University (VGU) Regional and Urban Planning Engineer at Ton Duc Thang University (TDTU) International Experiences Urban designer at B+H Architects Urban and Landscape designer at Lascal </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B.Sc. An Le</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-le-an/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-le-an/</guid>
      <description>Courses Urban Data Analytics Digital tools &amp;amp; Big data Geographic Information System Smart City and Urban Intervention Academic and Research Profile Bachelor of Science in Advanced Program in Computer Sciece (2014-2019), Vietnam National University Ho Chi Minh City - University of Science, Ho Chi Minh Studying about Master of Smart City Engineering, Seoul National University(SNU)(2020-2022), South Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MBA. Truong My Hanh Trinh</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/mba-trinh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/mba-trinh/</guid>
      <description>Academic Master of Business Administration, University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (2012) Bachelor of Economics of International Trade, Foreign Trade University (2007) Experiences Manager and developer of international cooperation network at Ton Duc Thang University (2016 - 2020) Member of the Secretariat of the UCI International University Consortium (2019 – 2020) Organizer of short-term programs for international students at Ton Duc Thang University (2016 - 2020) Participating in organizing international events and seminars at Ton Duc Thang University (2016 - 2020) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MA. Lai Phuong Dung</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/phuong-dung/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/phuong-dung/</guid>
      <description>Academic Master of Logistics Management, Rotterdam Business School, Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences, the Netherlands, 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M.Sc. Hai Hoang</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-hai-hoang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/msc-hai-hoang/</guid>
      <description>Courses Basic StudioLab 2 Academic and Research Profile Master of Science , Architecture, Tampere University of Technology (2013-2019) Erasmus Exchange Programme, Computational Design and Construction, ICD, University of Stuttgart, (2015) Bachelor of Architecture, Ho Chi Minh University of Architecture (2006-2011) International Experiences Architect, SAMY ARKITEHDIT, Finland (2018-2019) Summer Architect, ARCHIMG, Germany (2015-2016) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MA. Trinh Quoc Thang</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/mar-thangtrinh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/mar-thangtrinh/</guid>
      <description>Academic and Research Profile Master, KU Leuven University, Belgium (2017) Bachelor, University of Architecture Ho Chi Minh city &amp;amp; KU Leuven University (2016) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le Trung Ba Van (Ivan)</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/intern-le-trung-ba-van/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/intern-le-trung-ba-van/</guid>
      <description>Experiences
Head of Communication, Vietnam School of Development (2021)
Content Writer, Vietnam Halography, RIO Agency (2021)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le Phuc Toan</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/le-phuc-toan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/members/le-phuc-toan/</guid>
      <description>Designing media products. Developing products for research and training at ISCM.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
