<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Institute of Smart City &amp; Management</title>
    <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Institute of Smart City &amp; Management</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2021 by [ISCM](https://iscm.ueh.edu.vn)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ISCM PARTICIPATES IN THE VIETNAM URBAN FORUM 2024 WITH SUSTAINABLE PLANNING SOLUTIONS FOR TAM THANH, TAM KY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/20241112-iscm-at-vn-urbanforum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/20241112-iscm-at-vn-urbanforum/</guid>
      <description>Representing the design team from the Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM) - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH), MSc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City attends the 12th World Urban Forum in Cairo, Egypt</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/wuf12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/wuf12/</guid>
      <description>On November 4–8, 2024, the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH) attended the 12th World Urban Forum (WUF12) in Cairo, Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🤝HOSTING THE DELEGATION FROM THE LEE KUAN YEW CENTRE FOR INNOVATIVE CITIES, SINGAPORE UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY AND DESIGN, AT THE INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT (ISCM)</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/recap-chuy%E1%BA%BFn-th%C4%83m-v%C3%A0-l%C3%A0m-vi%E1%BB%87c-c%E1%BB%A7a-sutd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/recap-chuy%E1%BA%BFn-th%C4%83m-v%C3%A0-l%C3%A0m-vi%E1%BB%87c-c%E1%BB%A7a-sutd/</guid>
      <description>On November 1, 2024, the Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM) hosted representatives from the Lee Kuan Yew Centre for Innovative Cities (LKYCIC) at the Singapore University of Technology and Design (SUTD) to visit and work at ISCM’s Studiolab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLLABORATING WITH OVER 6 UNIVERSITIES IN SPAIN AND CHINA, ISCM PARTICIPATES IN AN ONLINE COURSE ON ARCHITECTURE, CITY, AND EAST ASIAN CULTURE</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/241021-chuoi-bai-hoc-online-ulyssess-hvk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/241021-chuoi-bai-hoc-online-ulyssess-hvk/</guid>
      <description>On October 21, lecturers from the Institute of Smart City and Management at the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH - ISCM) delivered a lecture as part of the Ulysses Online Course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTIFIC CONFERENCE ON SOLUTIONS TO ACCELERATE DIGITAL TRANSFORMATION IN SMART CITY DEVELOPMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/241026-hoi-thao-khoa-hoc-thuc-day-hoat-dong-chuyen-doi-so/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/241026-hoi-thao-khoa-hoc-thuc-day-hoat-dong-chuyen-doi-so/</guid>
      <description>On the afternoon of October 23, 2024, the scientific conference &amp;ldquo;Solutions to Accelerate Digital Transformation in Smart City Development&amp;rdquo; took place successfully at the Riverside Palace Convention Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOOKING BACK AT THE WORKSHOP: &#34;WHAT CONSTITUTES A SUCCESSFUL FEASIBILITY STUDY FOR THE RENOVATION OF SAI GON’S OLD PORT - CANG KHANH HOI?&#34;</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/ws_khanh_hoi_port/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/ws_khanh_hoi_port/</guid>
      <description>The workshop titled &amp;ldquo;What Constitutes a Successful Feasibility Study for the Renovation of Saigon’s Old Port - Cang Khanh Hoi?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOR THE FIRST TIME, ISCM SUPPORT ON HOSTING THE SOUTHEAST ASIA CONFERENCE OF THE AMERICAN INSTITUTE OF ARCHITECTS IN VIETNAM</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/recap_aia_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/recap_aia_2024/</guid>
      <description>On August 30, 2024, the Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM), in collaboration with the American Institute of Architects (AIA) in Southeast Asia and other partners, hosted the AIA Manila Southeast Asia Conference with the theme to celebrate Health, Well-being, and Sustainable Design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPLORING CAM LAM - KHANH HOA THROUGH THE LENS OF THE INTERNATIONAL SUMMER CAMP &#34;URBAN BEYOND THE URBAN 2024”</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/ubu2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/ubu2024/</guid>
      <description>At the end of July 2024, the Institute of Smart City and Management, in collaboration with Handong Global University (Korea), Ngurah Rai University (Indonesia), KU Leuven University (Belgium), and the University of Trieste (Italy), organized the International Summer Camp &amp;ldquo;Urban Beyond the Urban 2024&amp;rdquo; in Cam Lam - Khanh Hoa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEVELOPMENT OF THE DIGITAL ECONOMY: CONTRIBUTING TO THE CREATION OF A SMART CITY IN HO CHI MINH CITY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/digitaleconomy_hcmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/digitaleconomy_hcmc/</guid>
      <description>Aim to propose models, measurement indicators, as well as specific solutions to develop core digital economic sectors in Ho Chi Minh City, the Department of Information and Communications HCMC has led research projects on Digital Economy in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UEH, IN COLLABORATION WITH THU DUC CITY PEOPLE&#39;S COMMITTEE, SUCCESSFULLY HELD THE CONFERENCE DIGITAL ECONOMY - DRIVING FORCE FOR THU DUC CITY&#39;S DEVELOPMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/kts_thuduc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/kts_thuduc/</guid>
      <description>On July 30, 2024, the Institute of Regional Development Research and Consulting (IRDRC), the Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM) under the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH), and the Department of Science, Technology, and Information of Thu Duc City under the People&amp;rsquo;s Committee of Thu Duc City successfully organized the conference titled &amp;ldquo;Digital Economy - Driving Force for Thu Duc City&amp;rsquo;s Development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PODCAST] SUSTAINABLE UNIVERSITY MODEL FOR EMERGING MARKETS</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/podcast/</guid>
      <description>Today, the sustainable university model plays an important role in developing countries; in contrast, many difficulties in the implementation phase are available due to the limited autonomy and specific social factors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEMORANDUM OF UNDERSTANDING SIGNED BETWEEN THE INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT (UEH - ISCM) AND THE LEE KUAN YEW CENTRE FOR INNOVATIVE CITIES</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/sutd_mou/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/sutd_mou/</guid>
      <description>On July 17, 2024, the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City - represented by the Institute of Smart City and Management) and the Singapore University of Technology and Design (represented by the Lee Kuan Yew Centre for Innovative Cities) officially signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALK SHOW WHAT I TALK ABOUT WHEN I TALK ABOUT ARCHITECTURE? THE STUDY AND CAREER STORIES OF YOUNG VIETNAMESE ARCHITECTS</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/03072024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/03072024/</guid>
      <description>On July 6, 2024, the Institute of Smart City and Management, in collaboration with its partners, organized the seminar &amp;ldquo;What I Talk About When I Talk About Architecture?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPLORING DA LAT THROUGH THE LENS OF K49 ISCM STUDENTS WITH STUDIOLAB ARCHITECTURE 1: RESIDENTIAL PROJECT</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/studioarchitechture1_k49ueh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/studioarchitechture1_k49ueh/</guid>
      <description>From June 12 to June 15, 2024, Da Lat was the destination for the first field trip of the 49th cohort of students specializing in Architectural and Urban Design Inclusive Smart City Bachelor Program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISCUSSION WITH EXPERTS AT THE WORKSHOP: LIVING LAB MODEL AND PRACTICAL APPLICATIONS FOR HO CHI MINH CITY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2024-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2024-08/</guid>
      <description>On June 6, 2024, the Institute of Smart Cities and Management, in collaboration with Ong&amp;amp;Ong Vietnam and other partners, successfully organized the Workshop on Living Lab Model and Practical Applications at Studiolab—a knowledge hub connecting Vietnam with the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THAT IS THE CONCLUDE OF THE DEMO CLASS 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/lop_hoc_thu_2024_baud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/lop_hoc_thu_2024_baud/</guid>
      <description>Students, Lecturers, and Parents participated in the event&#xA;On May 12, 2024, the 2024 Demo Class of the Architectural and Urban Design Inclusive Smart City Bachelor Program, themed &amp;ldquo;Dare to Think - Dare to Dream,&amp;rdquo; officially came to a close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFERENCE ON RESEARCHING THE DEVELOPMENT OF DIGITAL ECONOMY IN HO CHI MINH CITY: EFFORTS TOWARDS A SMART AND SUSTAINABLE URBAN FUTURE</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/hoi_thao_kinh_te_so_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/hoi_thao_kinh_te_so_2024/</guid>
      <description>On April 26, 2024, the Department of Information and Communications of Ho Chi Minh City, in collaboration with the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City, organized the &amp;ldquo;Conference on Researching the Development of Digital Economy in Ho Chi Minh City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A JOURNEY, 6 AWARDS - 20 UEH REPRESENTATIVES EXCEL IN CONNECTING HERITAGE AND URBANISM TOWARDS SUSTAINABILITY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2024-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2024-04/</guid>
      <description>From April 20th to April 24th, 2024, 20 students along with 5 professors from the Architectural and Urban Design inclusive Smart City Program represented the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH) at the 14th National Architecture Student Festival in Hue City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOURNEY FOR THE FUTURE TALKSHOW: EMPOWERING K47 GRADUATES WITH CONFIDENCE FOR INTERNSHIP PHASE</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/intern_talkshow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/intern_talkshow/</guid>
      <description>Held on the morning of April 13, 2024, the &amp;ldquo;Journey for the Future&amp;rdquo; talkshow was a successful event that provided students of the 47 batch of the Architectural and Urban Design Inclusive Smart City program with the confidence to step into the internship phase equipped with standardized resumes, portfolios, and effective interview skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASTER&#39;S STUDENTS IN THE SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT PROGRAM FROM KHANH HOA PROVINCE WENT ON A PRACTICAL TRIP TO HO CHI MINH CITY.</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/15042024_master/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/15042024_master/</guid>
      <description>On April 12, 2024, as part of the City Project subjects, officials from Khanh Hoa province, enrolled in the Master&amp;rsquo;s program in Smart City and Innovation Management, conducted a field trip to various exemplary projects and campuses of the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH) throughout Ho Chi Minh City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTENSIVE WORKSHOP THANH DA - THE URBAN HIDDEN OASIS: THE UNTOLD STORY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/ws_thanhda_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/ws_thanhda_2024/</guid>
      <description>From March 18th to April 3rd, 2024, students of Architectural and Urban Design inclusive Smart City Bachelor Program embarked on an exhilarating experiential journey as they directly analyzed and proposed ideas for the Thanh Da Peninsula at the Workshop: Thanh Da - The Hidden Urban Oasis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEETING BETWEEN THE INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT AND THE PORTLAND STATE UNIVERSITY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2024-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2024-03/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Trinh Tu Anh and professors from Portland State University discussing research and educational activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAREER GUIDANCE &amp; ADMISSIONS DAY AT BACH KHOA UNIVERSITY: CONNECTING WITH THE ISCM ADVISORY TEAM AND STUDENTS</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2024-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2024-02/</guid>
      <description>🥰Last Sunday, on March 3, 2024, the Institute of Smart City and Management - the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH) had the opportunity to meet directly with parents and students from various provinces and cities at the Career Guidance &amp;amp; Admissions day 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXECUTIVE MASTER PROGRAM IN SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT: PRACTICAL APPROACH WITH A STUDY TOUR IN BANGKOK (THAILAND)</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/masterthailandtrip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/masterthailandtrip/</guid>
      <description>From February 21 to February 24, 2024, within the framework of the course on Smart and Sustainable Urban Measurement, students of the Executive Master Program in Smart City and Innovation Management had the opportunity to gain practical insights through a study trip in the capital city of Bangkok, Thailand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEMORANDUM OF UNDERSTANDING BETWEEN PLAYZ EDUTAINMENT AND INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/playzedu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/playzedu/</guid>
      <description>On January 29, the Institute of Smart Cities and Management (UEH - ISCM) and Playz Edutainment officially signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL SHORT COURSE IN SINGAPORE 2024: BASE FOR YOUNG RESEARCHERS</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/sutd-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/sutd-course/</guid>
      <description>From January 15 to January 26, 2024, the Institute of Smart City and Management - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH - ISCM) collaborated with the Lee Kuan Yew Centre for Innovative Cities at the Singapore University of Technology and Design (SUTD - LKYCIC) to organize a Short-Term International Course: Smart City and Technology - the Case of Ho Chi Minh City and Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOOKING BACK AT THE SERIES OF VUNG TAU FUTURE EVENTS IN VUNG TAU CITY IN 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/vung_tau_future_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/vung_tau_future_2024/</guid>
      <description>On January 9, 2024, University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City, in conjunction with the People&amp;rsquo;s Committee of Vung Tau City and partners organized Vung Tau Future event series, including the exhibition, International Conference “Developing Vung Tau City into a high-quality, world-class tourism city”, and the Award Ceremony of the 3rd International Design Competition: Reimagining Cities towards Carbon Neutrality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K47 ISCM AND RESILIENT LANDSCAPE DESIGN STUDIO: CONTRIBUTE TO A BLUE-GREEN NETWORK IN THU DUC CITY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2024-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2024-01/</guid>
      <description>By the end of 2023, the students&amp;rsquo; final presentation took place for the resilient landscape design studio of the third bachelor year at UEH University, Ho Chi Minh City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEMINAR: GREEN GROWTH - AN OPPORTUNITY FOR LOCAL DEVELOPMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-57/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-57/</guid>
      <description>🌳On October 28, 2023, the Institute of Smart City and Management - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH - ISCM) cooperated with Green+ Group Joint Stock Company to organize the Seminar Green Growth - An opportunity for Local Development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASIC STUDIOLAB 3 &amp; HISTORY OF ARCHITECTURE AND URBANISM EXHIBITION OF BATCH 48</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-55/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-55/</guid>
      <description>One of the indispensable activities of the students of Architecture and Urban Design Inclusive Smart City, in the past few days, the Exhibition of Batch 48 ISCM students has officially returned with completely new works from two subjects: Basic Studiolab 3, and History of Architecture and Urbanism .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPERIENCE NEW TECHNOLOGY WITH WORKSHOP COMPUTER VISION IN MOBILITY ANALYSIS</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-56/</guid>
      <description>🧑‍💻On October 20, 2023, the Institute of Smart City and Management held a Workshop: Computer Vision in Mobility Analysis with the participation of students from different majors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDIOLAB ARCHITECTURE 2 COURSE: EXPLORE THE ARCHITECTURE OF AUDI TAN BINH SHOWROOM</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-53/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday (October 4), ISCM students had a field trip to the showroom of Audi Tan Binh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISCM STUDENTS AND STUDIOLAB ARCHITECTURE COURSE 2: THE EXPLORATION OF PORSCHE CENTRE SAIGON</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-54/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-54/</guid>
      <description>🏁Exquisite architecture combined with a strong sports car spirit;&#xA;🌐The first center in the Asia-Pacific region to fully adopt the latest Destination Porsche architectural concept, setting new standards in design, construction, maintenance, and operations for future Porsche centers in the region;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A MILESTONE TO UNLEASH YOUR CONFIDENCE, CONSTRUCT YOUR VERY OWN UTOPIA</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-51/</guid>
      <description>On September 24, 2023, the traditional Welcome festival of students from the Institute of Smart City and Management - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH-ISCM) has officially returned, welcoming Batch 49 - the youngest generation of the Bachelor of Architectural and Urban Design Inclusive Smart City program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT ORGANIZE ORIENTATION DAY 2023: DESIGN YOUR UTOPIA WELCOME NEW STUDENTS OF THE BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURAL AND URBAN DESIGN INCLUSIVE SMART CITY PROGRAM</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-50/</guid>
      <description>The traditional first year festival of students of the Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM) - Ho Chi Minh City University of Economics (UEH) has officially returned, welcoming the youngest student of class 49 to the Architecture and Design program Smart Urban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROUTE2SCHOOL VIRTUAL REALITY CYCLING AT AI4VN 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-49/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-49/</guid>
      <description>On September 21-22, University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH) participated in the AI Expo exhibition, within the Vietnam Artificial Intelligence Festival (AI4VN 2023).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIMATE STORY WORKSHOP: EXPLORING THE INTERSECTION OF ARTS, SCIENCE, AND TECHNOLOGY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-48/</guid>
      <description>Recently, on September 6, 2023, Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM), in collaboration with UK audiovisual artist collective D-Fuse and Vietnam creative studio Phố Bên Đồi, cordially invites you to join the bilingual workshop “Climate story”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1ST SMART CITY EDUCATION SYMPOSIUM: SMART URBAN INTERVENTION - SMART CITY LIVING LAB (SCLL) 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-33/</guid>
      <description>Smart city initiatives address the challenges of urbanization, with a focus on improving the quality of life in an inclusive and sustainable way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISCOVERY: NORTH PHUOC THANG ECOLOGICAL URBAN AREA OF VUNG TAU CITY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-41/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-41/</guid>
      <description>🌴North Phuoc Thang, the chosen site for the 3rd International Design Competition: Reimagining Cities towards Carbon Neutrality has a beautiful landscape of aquaculture and mangrove ecology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTNERSHIPS NEWS | MEETING BETWEEN INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT - UNIVERSITY OF ECONOMICS HO CHI MINH CITY (UEH-ISCM), XI&#39;AN JIAOTONG-LIVERPOOL UNIVERSITY (CHINA), SUNGKYUNKWAN UNIVERSITY, JUNGLIM ARCHITECTURE, AND KOREA ADVANCED INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY (KOREA)</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-43/</guid>
      <description>Last week, the Institute of Smart City and Management - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH-ISCM) has met and worked with a delegation of professors and experts from Xi&amp;rsquo;an Jiaotong-Liverpool University (China), Sungkyunkwan University, Junglim Architecture, and Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (Korea).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REWIND: 1ST SMART CITY EDUCATION SYMPOSIUM: SMART URBAN INTERVENTION - SMART CITY LIVING LAB (SCLL) 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-42/</guid>
      <description>On August 17, the first Education Symposium: Smart Urban Intervention - Smart City Living Lab (SCLL) in 2023 was held by the Institute of Smart City and Management - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH-ISCM), Thu Duc City Authority in cooperation with Xi&amp;rsquo;an Jiaotong-Liverpool University (China) and Sungkyunkwan University (Korea).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> THROWBACK - EDUCATION SYMPOSIUM: SMART CITY DEVELOPMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-39/</guid>
      <description>🏙️ Last Monday, the Education Symposium: Smart City Development was held successfully, with the participation of professors and experts in Smart Cities, Mobility Planning, Urban Planning, together with PhD students, as well as university students from University of Seoul (Korea), University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City, University of Architecture Ho Chi Minh City, and Hasselt University (Belgium).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTNERSHIP NEWS | MEETING BETWEEN UNIVERSITY OF SEOUL (KOREA) AND INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT - UNIVERSITY OF ECONOMICS HO CHI MINH CITY (UEH-ISCM)</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-40/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the Institute of Smart City and Management - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH-ISCM) was pleased to welcome the University of Seoul (UoS - Korea) to come and visit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTNERSHIP NEWS | MEETING BETWEEN INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT - UEH COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY AND DESIGN (ISCM), HANDONG GLOBAL UNIVERSITY (KOREA), AND THAMMASAT UNIVERSITY (THAILAND)</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-35/</guid>
      <description>On Friday, August 4, 2023, amidst the International Summer Course &amp;ldquo;Urban Beyond the Urban&amp;rdquo; held in Bangkok, representatives of the Institute of Smart City and Management - UEH College of Technology and Design (ISCM), Handong Global University (Korea), and Faculty of Architecture and Urban Planning - Thammasat University (Thailand), had a meeting and discussion around shaping the future of smart cities and urban planning, aligning with shared vision of sustainable and innovative urban development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTNERSHIP NEWS | MEETING BETWEEN CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) AND INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT - UEH COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY AND DESIGN (ISCM)</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-34/</guid>
      <description>On Thursday, August 3, 2023, the Faculty of Architecture at Chulalongkorn University hosted a meeting to foster academic and research collaboration with the Institute of Smart City and Management, UEH College of Technology and Design (UEH-CTD-ISCM).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL SUMMER COURSE URBAN BEYOND THE URBAN IN BANGKOK, THAILAND: UNDERSTANDING LOCAL TOURISM AND SUSTAINABLE MOBILITY THROUGH RESEARCH AND EXPERIENCE.</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-38/</guid>
      <description>INTERNATIONAL SUMMER COURSE URBAN BEYOND THE URBAN IN BANGKOK, THAILAND: UNDERSTANDING LOCAL TOURISM AND SUSTAINABLE MOBILITY THROUGH RESEARCH AND EXPERIENCE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL SUMMER COURSE URBAN BEYOND THE URBAN IN NHA TRANG: INTEGRATE MULTI-PERSPECTIVE TO DELVE INTO NIGHT ECONOMY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-30/</guid>
      <description>INTERNATIONAL SUMMER COURSE URBAN BEYOND THE URBAN IN NHA TRANG: INTEGRATE MULTI-PERSPECTIVE TO DELVE INTO NIGHT ECONOMY</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARBON NEUTRALITY: A CONCEPT TO FOLLOW IN REIMAGINING CITIES PROCESS</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-47/</guid>
      <description>Occupied a certain portion in the criteria of the 3rd International Design Competition, Carbon Neutrality is demonstrated as the balance between emitting carbon and absorbing carbon from the atmosphere in carbon sinks [1]- which is described as any system that absorbs more carbon than it releases, for example forests, oceans and soil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A LOOK AT SEAUS INTERNATIONAL SCIENCE CONFERENCE 2023: URBAN DESIGN SOLUTIONS IN SOUTHEAST ASIA TO SOLVE GLOBAL Warming</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-25/</guid>
      <description>RECAP SEAUS 2023 International Scientific Conference: Urban Design Solutions In Southeast Asia Towards Solving The Problem Of Global Warming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPLORE: VUNG TAU COASTAL CITY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-37/</guid>
      <description>As a place where the chosen site challenges our talented competitors in the 3rd International Design Competition: Reimagining Cities towards Carbon Neutrality located, Vung Tau coastal city has its own prospects, which can be utilized in its process of developing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEYNOTE SPEAKERS ANNOUNCEMENT OF THE 1ST REGIONAL CONFERENCE: SOUTH EAST ASIAN URBANISMS TO ADDRESS GLOBAL WARMING</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-23/</guid>
      <description>🌳 Date: 8AM - May 30, 2023&#xA;🌳 Venues: Main Lecture Hall, the University of Economics HCMC (UEH), 59C Nguyen Dinh Chieu, Vo Thi Sau Ward, District 3, HCMC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UEH STUDENTS WIN RUNNER-UP ULI HINES STUDENTS COMPETITION FOR THE FIRST TIME ORGANIZED IN ASIAN - PACIFIC</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-27/</guid>
      <description>With the advice of Mr. Pablo Acebillo (Manager of Master Planning and Design, enCity), Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAKE A LOOK INTO THE NEWEST COLORFUL AND CREATIVE ZONE OF UEH UNIVERSITY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-22/</guid>
      <description>🔭Guess what? UEH MakerSpace - a completely new creative space - will soon be officially launched on the ground floor of B2, for UEHers and the community who love activities related to Design, Assembly, Woodworking, as well as enjoying a great space for group activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONVOCATION CEREMONY OF MASTER OF SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT FOR KHANH HOA PROVINCE</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-15/</guid>
      <description>On April 8th, 2023, the Convocation ceremony of the Master of Smart City and Innovation Management course for the officials working at many departments of Khanh Hoa Province was held successfully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECAP - DEMO CLASS: FROM DREAM TO LIFE - BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURAL AND URBAN DESIGN INCLUSIVE SMART CITY PROGRAM</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-13/</guid>
      <description>🎉 On April 1st, 2023, the Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM) in collaboration with the Department of Student Affairs (DSA), UEH Smart Library successfully organized the program Demo Class: “From Dream to Life - Bachelor of Architectural and Urban Design Inclusive Smart City Program”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RECAP] CAREER GUIDANCE &amp; ADMISSIONS FESTIVAL 26/02/2023 : ARCHITECTURE IS NOT THAT HARD, SINCE HERE COMES ISCM</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-08/</guid>
      <description>[RECAP] CAREER GUIDANCE &amp;amp; ADMISSIONS FESTIVAL 26/02/2023 : ARCHITECTURE IS NOT THAT HARD, SINCE HERE COMES ISCM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEMORANDUM OF UNDERSTANDING SIGN CEREMONY BETWEEN UEH COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY AND DESIGN AND ENCITY INTERNATIONAL CONSULTING JOINT STOCK COMPANY; INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT (ISCM) AND UNIVERSITY-INDUSTRY FOUNDATION, YONSEI UNIVERSITY; ISCM AND INSTITUTE OF ECONOMIC RESEARCH - KOREA UNIVERSITY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-06/</guid>
      <description>On the afternoon of February 15, 2023, at Campus 232/6 Vo Thi Sau Street, the Memorandum of Understanding Sign ceremony between: UEH College of Technology and Design (UEH-CTD) and enCity International Consulting Joint Stock Company (enCity); Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM) and University - Industry Foundation, Yonsei University (YUIF); ISCM and Institute of Economic Research - Korea University (KU-IER) was held successfully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RECAP] WORKSHOP: URBAN SKETCH AT CITY THEATER &amp; BEN THANH MARKET, HCMC</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-07/</guid>
      <description>In the last two days 12 &amp;amp; 13, UEH - Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM - UEH), in collaboration with Urban Sketchers Vietnam, organized Workshop: Urban Sketch - an open activity of the event series in 2023 of ISCM with the theme: “Design for Carbon Neutrality Future”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASTER ORIENTATION DAY - A SPECIAL GREETING FOR THE MASTER OF SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-04/</guid>
      <description>MASTER ORIENTATION DAY - A SPECIAL GREETING FOR THE MASTER OF SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISCM 2022  IN REVIEW</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-03/</guid>
      <description>At ISCM, this past year has been filled with many highlights and memorable memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INPUT 2023] [SESSION] RESILIENT, CIRCULAR AND SUSTAINABLE CITIES</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2023-02/</guid>
      <description>The Circular City paradigm contains not only principles of the Circular Economy (recovery, recycling, reuse and sharing), but also the introductions of actions related to the development of renewable energy communities, use of green materials and CO2 uptake, Triple Access Planning (TAP).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REWIND] READY FOR NEXT: INTERNATIONAL SCIENTIFIC CONFERENCE: A FUTURE RESILIENCE THROUGH SMART CITY LENS (FR)</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-50/</guid>
      <description>[REWIND] READY FOR NEXT: INTERNATIONAL SCIENTIFIC CONFERENCE: A FUTURE RESILIENCE THROUGH SMART CITY LENS (FR)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READY FOR NEXT UEH 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-43/</guid>
      <description>Realizing the important role of universities and colleges in maintaining cultural, artistic and historical heritages associated with SDG11 in 17 sustainable development goals of the United Nations, besides training, research, operation, and university governance towards Multidisciplinary and Sustainability, University of Economics HCMC considers nurturing a community to encourage change and inspire the arts towards sustainable development actions one of its strategic pillars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READY FOR NEXT 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-42/</guid>
      <description>After more than a hinge year (September 2021 - November 2022) officially restructuring with the strategy of a Multidisciplinary and Sustainable University, UEH today with 46 years as the foundation and the driving force is Ready to transform into a Multidisciplinary and Sustainable UEH of Tomorrow “UEH - Ready for Next”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#LifeatISCM | K48’S FIRST UNIVERSITY MONTH AT ISMC - MORE THAN A JOURNEY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-41/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-41/</guid>
      <description>For over a month, the ISCM team accompanied and followed our students as they took their first subjects, marveling at their hidden creativity and clear progress with each lesson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECAP: SUSTAINALE FASHION</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-15/</guid>
      <description>It is surveyed that the fashion industry is now the second greatest factor that pollutes the environment, just after the gas industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RECAP] ORIENTATION DAY K48 - BE THE SUN </title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-17/</guid>
      <description>It has been several weeks since the ORIENTATION DAY for K48 - especially for freshmen from the Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM) and the School of Media Design (SMD), occurred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL WORKSHOP: GLOBAL CITY DEVELOPMENT CAMP - ORIENTATION DAY - THE BEGINNING OF MIRACLE MEETING</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/international-workshop-global-city-development-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/international-workshop-global-city-development-camp/</guid>
      <description>About Event Now in Vinh Long city, going through a difficult time of Covid 19, the magical meeting between Korean and Vietnamese students officially occurred after more than a few months of preparation and waiting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISCM &amp; KOREA TRIP: CONNECTING COOPERATION AND MORE</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-06/</guid>
      <description>As part of a series of events to foster collaboration with universities around the world as part of the 2022 - A Future Resilience Through Smart City Lens event series, the Institute of Smart City and Management had a field trip from August 22-30 to experience, discuss cooperation with various smart city research agencies and units as well as universities in Korea, one of the leading countries in smart city development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K47 BAUD - Architectural Studiolab 1 - TIMELAPSE VIDEO</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-04/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s watch with ISCM the time-lapse video of Architectural Studiolab 1 of our students!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEARN, WORK, AND DEVELOP TOGETHER AT ISCM</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-26/</guid>
      <description>Whether it is the beginning of the week or the weekend, day or night, our students - the first generation of Bachelor Of Architectural And Urban Design Inclusive Smart City are still tediously completing Architectural Studiolab 1 day and night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECAP INTERNATIONAL WORKSHOP WEEK: GLOBAL CITY DEVELOPMENT CAMP</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-03/</guid>
      <description>RECAP INTERNATIONAL WORKSHOP WEEK: GLOBAL CITY DEVELOPMENT CAMP Since 2020, the International Workshop has successfully connected and shared knowledge among project members, providing participants with multi-dimensional perspectives that facilitate problem-solving, practical application of knowledge, and unforgettable experiences with international friends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THROWBACK TEAM BUILDING - LEARN HARD, PLAY HARD</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-27/</guid>
      <description>Learning without playing loses youth, learning while playing invites you to ISCM - where students study hard and play enthusiastically!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL WORKSHOP: GLOBAL CITY DEVELOPMENT CAMP - ORIENTATION DAY - THE BEGINNING OF MIRACLE MEETING</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-international-workshop-global-city-development-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-international-workshop-global-city-development-camp/</guid>
      <description>About Event Now in Vinh Long city, going through a difficult time of Covid 19, the magical meeting between Korean and Vietnamese students officially occurred after more than a few months of preparation and waiting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FROM UEH HO CHI MINH CITY CAMPUS  TO UEH VINH LONG BRANCH - THE FIRST CAMPUS TRANSFER PROGRAM IN UEH FOR BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURAL AND URBAN DESIGN INCLUSIVE SMART CITY (BAUD)</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-05/</guid>
      <description>In addition to studying in modern Studiolab, ISCM always strives to provide learners with the most practical experience to understand the industry and provide learners with multi-dimensional perspectives and ways of thinking, which encourages learners to continuously expand the framework of creativity, thinking, and vision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENROLMENT OPEN SEASON 2 - MASTER OF SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-23/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, social issues, policies, urban planning, and sustainable development are receiving substantial attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECAP WORKSHOP ART SUMMER CAMP FOR KIDS</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-30/</guid>
      <description>Art is the path to the creative power within each child and “every child is an artist” (Pablo Picasso).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RECAP] TUOI TRE NEWSPAPERS’ UNIVERSTY ENROLLMENT CONSULTANT 2022 FESTIVALS</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-34/</guid>
      <description>Tuoi Tre Newspapers’ University enrollment consultant 2022 festivals, held at Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology (HCMUT), has officially come to the end with a lively and full of energy atmosphere from not only the students but also the parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISCM STUDIOLAB - THE &#34;INTELLIGENT TRANSFORMATION&#34; SPACE IN UEH</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-36/</guid>
      <description>ISCM STUDIOLAB - THE &amp;ldquo;INTELLIGENT TRANSFORMATION&amp;rdquo; SPACE IN UEH&#xA;At Vo Thi Sau campus (District 3), ISCM&amp;rsquo;s Studiolab is a place to provide modern technology experiences, smart city simulation, and especially possessing the ability to transform intelligently when it can transform into a space for research, teaching, art gallery, or even studio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISCM STUDIOLAB - SPACE OF MODERN EXPERIENCE INTEGRATION</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-37/</guid>
      <description>ISCM STUDIOLAB - SPACE OF MODERN EXPERIENCE INTEGRATION&#xA;ISCM is proud to own Studiolab, which provides modern technology experiences, smart city simulation, and a smart space for multipurpose use such as teaching, research, &amp;hellip; and even a movie studio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISCM EXPERIENCED PORSCHE SAI GON SHOWROOM</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-01-16_porsche/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-01-16_porsche/</guid>
      <description>On January 16, the ISCM team and students were honoured to represent UEH University to attend the Porsche Saigon experience in Ho Chi Minh City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST STUDENTS OF THE EXECUTIVE MASTER OF SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT PROGRAMS</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-24/</guid>
      <description>This is a photo of our very first students of the Executive Master of Smart City and Innovation Management programs, who were studying Data Analysis &amp;amp; Data Mining in the Studiolab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2021 - REFLECTION AND HAPPY NEW YEAR</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-40/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2022-40/</guid>
      <description>As 2021 draws to a close, we would like to encourage you to join us in reflecting on the last episode of the event series SMARTCITY+ 2021 and ready for a special next year!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACHELOR ORIENTATION DAY-DREAM RIGHT-DREAM SAO-CHO ĐÚNG</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2021-ba-orientation-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2021-ba-orientation-day/</guid>
      <description>____________&#xA;In our dreams, between virtual and real, there is always a significant gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORIENTATION DAY - MASTER OF SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2021-masterorientation-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/2021-masterorientation-day/</guid>
      <description>____________&#xA;The Institute of Smart Cities and Management (ISCM) is delighted to welcome the first generation of the Executive Master of Smart City and Innovation courses in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE OPENING CEREMONY OF THE CITY SCIENCE LAB  HO CHI MINH CITY</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/the-opening-ceremony-of-the-city-science-lab-ho-chi-minh-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/the-opening-ceremony-of-the-city-science-lab-ho-chi-minh-city/</guid>
      <description>In the morning of April 22, 2021, the opening ceremony of the City Science Lab @ Ho Chi Minh City (CSL @ HCMC) was successfully celebrated at 422 Vo Van Kiet Street, Co Giang ward, District 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUSTAINABLE URBAN DESIGN</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/thi%E1%BA%BFt-k%E1%BA%BF-%C4%91%C3%B4-th%E1%BB%8B-t%E1%BA%A7m-nh%C3%ACn-v%E1%BB%AFng-ch%E1%BA%AFc-cho-%C4%91%C3%B4-th%E1%BB%8B-b%E1%BB%81n-v%E1%BB%AFng/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/thi%E1%BA%BFt-k%E1%BA%BF-%C4%91%C3%B4-th%E1%BB%8B-t%E1%BA%A7m-nh%C3%ACn-v%E1%BB%AFng-ch%E1%BA%AFc-cho-%C4%91%C3%B4-th%E1%BB%8B-b%E1%BB%81n-v%E1%BB%AFng/</guid>
      <description>About Event On March 25, in Ho Chi Minh City, the Institute of Smart Cities and Management, in cooperation with B+H, held a webinar with the theme &amp;ldquo;A new understanding of the imperative of healthy city design&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECOVERY OF TRAVEL AND EFFORTS TO ESCAPE FROM THE WHIRLWIND INFLUENCED BY COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/ph%E1%BB%A5c-h%E1%BB%93i-du-l%E1%BB%8Bch-v%C3%A0-n%E1%BB%97-l%E1%BB%B1c-tho%C3%A1t-kh%E1%BB%8Fi-v%C3%B2ng-xo%C3%A1y-%E1%BA%A3nh-h%C6%B0%E1%BB%9Fng-b%E1%BB%9Fi-covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/ph%E1%BB%A5c-h%E1%BB%93i-du-l%E1%BB%8Bch-v%C3%A0-n%E1%BB%97-l%E1%BB%B1c-tho%C3%A1t-kh%E1%BB%8Fi-v%C3%B2ng-xo%C3%A1y-%E1%BA%A3nh-h%C6%B0%E1%BB%9Fng-b%E1%BB%9Fi-covid-19/</guid>
      <description>About Event The year 2020 - 365 days of travel around the world were suspended and the phrase &amp;ldquo;closed&amp;rdquo; repeatedly appeared at tourist sites for the Covid epidemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORKSHOP AND WEBINAR WEEK &#34;STAYCATION, THE HOSPITABLE CITY - WHY NOT?&#34;</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/workshop-and-webinar-international-week-staycation-the-hospitable-city-why-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/workshop-and-webinar-international-week-staycation-the-hospitable-city-why-not/</guid>
      <description>On March 1st, 2021, the opening ceremony of workshop week with the theme “Global Strategies for Local Tourism” was successfully organized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CULTURE, COHESION AND CIVIC SOCIETY: HOW SMART CITIES BUILD ON THE BEST OF OUR PAST?</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/culture-cohesion-and-civic-society-how-smart-cities-build-on-the-best-of-our-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/culture-cohesion-and-civic-society-how-smart-cities-build-on-the-best-of-our-past/</guid>
      <description>About Event On December 21st, 2020, the webinar “Culture, Cohesion and Civic Society: How Smart Cities Build on the Best of Our Past?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UEH UNIVERSITY HOSTED THE SOUTHEAST REGION OF THE NATIONAL FESTIVAL FOR INNOVATIVE STARTUPS – TECHFEST 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/university-of-economics-ho-chi-minh-city-hosted-the-southeast-region-of-the-national-festival-for-innovative-startups--techfest-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/university-of-economics-ho-chi-minh-city-hosted-the-southeast-region-of-the-national-festival-for-innovative-startups--techfest-2020/</guid>
      <description>About Event On November 24, 2020, University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City hosted the Southeast Region of the national festival for innovative startups – TECHFEST 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL LAUNCH EVENT</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/international-launch-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 06:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/international-launch-event/</guid>
      <description>Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM)-University of Economics HCMC (UEH) today has successfully organized an international launch event, along with the prize-giving ceremony for the 1st international design contest “Future city: design for the post-pandemic world”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUTURE OUTLOOK</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/future-outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/future-outlook/</guid>
      <description>There is no doubt that the world is ever-changing, so planning a future outlook in which human always take the proactive role to operate is essential.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAUNCH EVENT: BAUD - BAS DUAL-DEGREE PROGRAM</title>
      <link>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/launch-event-baud-bas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.iscm.ueh.edu.vn/news/launch-event-baud-bas/</guid>
      <description>About Event On September 3, 2021, the Institute of Smart City and Management of the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City and the Faculty of Creative Arts and Industries of the University of Auckland successfully launched the Bachelor of Architecture and Urban Design (BAUD) and Bachelor of Architectural Studies (BAS) dual-degree programs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
