<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Institute of Smart City &amp; Management</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/event/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Institute of Smart City &amp; Management</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2021 by [ISCM](https://iscm.ueh.edu.vn)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OPEN FOR REGISTRATION | URBAN BEYOND THE URBAN PROGRAM IN 2024: CAM LAM - KHANH HOA</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2024-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2024-05/</guid>
      <description>🌳 Following the journey of 2023, the 2nd Urban Beyond the Urban (UBU) returns in 2024 with the theme “Smart Approach: Co-Design Platform &amp;amp; Nature-Based Solutions for Cam Lam, Khanh Hoa”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THAT IS THE CONCLUDE OF THE DEMO CLASS 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/lop_hoc_thu_2024_baud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/lop_hoc_thu_2024_baud/</guid>
      <description>Students, Lecturers, and Parents participated in the event&#xA;On May 12, 2024, the 2024 Demo Class of the Architectural and Urban Design Inclusive Smart City Bachelor Program, themed &amp;ldquo;Dare to Think - Dare to Dream,&amp;rdquo; officially came to a close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFERENCE ON RESEARCHING THE DEVELOPMENT OF DIGITAL ECONOMY IN HO CHI MINH CITY: EFFORTS TOWARDS A SMART AND SUSTAINABLE URBAN FUTURE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/hoi_thao_kinh_te_so_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/hoi_thao_kinh_te_so_2024/</guid>
      <description>On April 26, 2024, the Department of Information and Communications of Ho Chi Minh City, in collaboration with the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City, organized the &amp;ldquo;Conference on Researching the Development of Digital Economy in Ho Chi Minh City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A JOURNEY, 6 AWARDS - 20 UEH REPRESENTATIVES EXCEL IN CONNECTING HERITAGE AND URBANISM TOWARDS SUSTAINABILITY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2024-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2024-04/</guid>
      <description>From April 20th to April 24th, 2024, 20 students along with 5 professors from the Architectural and Urban Design inclusive Smart City Program represented the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH) at the 14th National Architecture Student Festival in Hue City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journey for the Future Talkshow: Empowering K47 Graduates with Confidence for Internship Phase</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/intern_talkshow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/intern_talkshow/</guid>
      <description>Held on the morning of April 13, 2024, the &amp;ldquo;Journey for the Future&amp;rdquo; talkshow was a successful event that provided students of the 47 batch of the Architectural and Urban Design Inclusive Smart City program with the confidence to step into the internship phase equipped with standardized resumes, portfolios, and effective interview skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASTER&#39;S STUDENTS IN THE SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT PROGAM FROM KHANH HOA PROVINCE WENT ON A PRACTICAL TRIP TO HO CHI MINH CITY.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/15042024_master/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/15042024_master/</guid>
      <description>On April 12, 2024, as part of the City Project subjects, officials from Khanh Hoa province, enrolled in the Master&amp;rsquo;s program in Smart City and Innovation Management, conducted a field trip to various exemplary projects and campuses of the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH) throughout Ho Chi Minh City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTENSIVE WORKSHOP THANH DA - THE URBAN HIDDEN OASIS: THE UNTOLD STORY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/ws_thanhda_2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/ws_thanhda_2024/</guid>
      <description>From March 18th to April 3rd, 2024, students of Architectural and Urban Design inclusive Smart City Bachelor Program embarked on an exhilarating experiential journey as they directly analyzed and proposed ideas for the Thanh Da Peninsula at the Workshop: Thanh Da - The Hidden Urban Oasis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAREER GUIDANCE &amp; ADMISSIONS DAY AT BACH KHOA UNIVERSITY: CONNECTING WITH THE ISCM ADVISORY TEAM AND STUDENTS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2024-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2024-02/</guid>
      <description>🥰Last Sunday, on March 3, 2024, the Institute of Smart City and Management - the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH) had the opportunity to meet directly with parents and students from various provinces and cities at the Career Guidance &amp;amp; Admissions day 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXECUTIVE MASTER PROGRAM IN SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT: PRACTICAL APPROACH WITH A STUDY TOUR IN BANGKOK (THAILAND)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/masterthailandtrip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/masterthailandtrip/</guid>
      <description>From February 21 to February 24, 2024, within the framework of the course on Smart and Sustainable Urban Measurement, students of the Executive Master Program in Smart City and Innovation Management had the opportunity to gain practical insights through a study trip in the capital city of Bangkok, Thailand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL SHORT COURSE IN SINGAPORE 2024: BASE FOR YOUNG RESEARCHERS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/sutd-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/sutd-course/</guid>
      <description>From January 15 to January 26, 2024, the Institute of Smart City and Management - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH - ISCM) collaborated with the Lee Kuan Yew Centre for Innovative Cities at the Singapore University of Technology and Design (SUTD - LKYCIC) to organize a Short-Term International Course: Smart City and Technology - the Case of Ho Chi Minh City and Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEMINAR: GREEN GROWTH - AN OPPORTUNITY FOR LOCAL DEVELOPMENT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-57/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-57/</guid>
      <description>🌳On October 28, 2023, the Institute of Smart City and Management - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH - ISCM) cooperated with Green+ Group Joint Stock Company to organize the Seminar Green Growth - An opportunity for Local Development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASIC STUDIOLAB 3 &amp; HISTORY OF ARCHITECTURE AND URBANISM EXHIBITION OF BATCH 48</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-55/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-55/</guid>
      <description>One of the indispensable activities of the students of Architecture and Urban Design Inclusive Smart City, in the past few days, the Exhibition of Batch 48 ISCM students has officially returned with completely new works from two subjects: Basic Studiolab 3, and History of Architecture and Urbanism .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPERIENCE NEW TECHNOLOGY WITH WORKSHOP COMPUTER VISION IN MOBILITY ANALYSIS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-56/</guid>
      <description>🧑‍💻On October 20, 2023, the Institute of Smart City and Management held a Workshop: Computer Vision in Mobility Analysis with the participation of students from different majors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A MILESTONE TO UNLEASH YOUR CONFIDENCE, CONSTRUCT YOUR VERY OWN UTOPIA</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-51/</guid>
      <description>On September 24, 2023, the traditional Welcome festival of students from the Institute of Smart City and Management - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH-ISCM) has officially returned, welcoming Batch 49 - the youngest generation of the Bachelor of Architectural and Urban Design Inclusive Smart City program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTITUTE OF SMART CITY AND MANAGEMENT ORGANIZE ORIENTATION DAY 2023: DESIGN YOUR UTOPIA WELCOME NEW STUDENTS OF THE BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURAL AND URBAN DESIGN INCLUSIVE SMART CITY PROGRAM</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-50/</guid>
      <description>The traditional first year festival of students of the Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM) - Ho Chi Minh City University of Economics (UEH) has officially returned, welcoming the youngest student of class 49 to the Architecture and Design program Smart Urban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIMATE STORY WORKSHOP: EXPLORING THE INTERSECTION OF ARTS, SCIENCE, AND TECHNOLOGY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-48/</guid>
      <description>Recently, on September 6, 2023, Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM), in collaboration with UK audiovisual artist collective D-Fuse and Vietnam creative studio Phố Bên Đồi, cordially invites you to join the bilingual workshop “Climate story”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDUCATIONAL SYMPOSIUM: SMART CITY DEVELOPMENT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-32/</guid>
      <description>EDUCATIONAL SYMPOSIUM: SMART CITY DEVELOPMENT&#xA;Being able to solve a majority of problems that cities are facing in the process of urbanization, Smart Cities are one of the inevitable trends in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7th COMMUNITY OF LEARNING AND PRACTICE (CoLP) WEBINAR: WALKABILITY TRANSITIONS - CASE STUDIES FROM PHILIPPINES, VIETNAM AND INDONESIA</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-31/</guid>
      <description>⏳Time: 2:00 PM (UTC +7:00) | 11/08/2023&#xA;🖥️Online via zoom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEN FOR REGISTRATION | DESIGN COMPETITION: YOUR STUDIO BOOKLET 2023-2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-36/</guid>
      <description>Providing an environment where students can express your personality, affirm their creativity and give them the opportunity to achieve the mentioned goals, the Design Competition with the theme &amp;ldquo;Your Booklet Studio&amp;rdquo; is officially opened for registration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL SUMMER COURSE URBAN BEYOND THE URBAN IN BANGKOK, THAILAND: UNDERSTANDING LOCAL TOURISM AND SUSTAINABLE MOBILITY THROUGH RESEARCH AND EXPERIENCE.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-38/</guid>
      <description>INTERNATIONAL SUMMER COURSE URBAN BEYOND THE URBAN IN BANGKOK, THAILAND: UNDERSTANDING LOCAL TOURISM AND SUSTAINABLE MOBILITY THROUGH RESEARCH AND EXPERIENCE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THERE IS LESS THAN 90 DAYS LEFT TO THE SUBMISSION DEADLINE OF THE THIRD INTERNATIONAL DESIGN COMPETITION: REIMAGINING CITIES TOWARDS CARBON NEUTRALITY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-29/</guid>
      <description>🌳 THERE IS LESS THAN 90 DAYS LEFT TO THE SUBMISSION DEADLINE OF THE THIRD INTERNATIONAL DESIGN COMPETITION: REIMAGINING CITIES TOWARDS CARBON NEUTRALITY</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL SUMMER COURSE URBAN BEYOND THE URBAN IN NHA TRANG: INTEGRATE MULTI-PERSPECTIVE TO DELVE INTO NIGHT ECONOMY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-30/</guid>
      <description>INTERNATIONAL SUMMER COURSE URBAN BEYOND THE URBAN IN NHA TRANG: INTEGRATE MULTI-PERSPECTIVE TO DELVE INTO NIGHT ECONOMY</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBU INTERNATIONAL SUMMER CAMP: LOCAL TOURISM AND SUSTAINABLE MOBILITY - BANGKOK, THAILAND</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-46/</guid>
      <description>The UBU International Summer Camp 2023 with the theme “Local Tourism and Sustainable Mobility” is NOW OPEN for official applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEMINAR - TRANSITION TOWARDS THE CIRCULAR ECONOMY: SMEs PERSPECTIVE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-44/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-44/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays, the Circular economy (CE) has been widely adopted by different business sizes and types, including SMEs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEBINAR MAXIMIZING ENERGY EFFICIENCY: SUSTAINABLE, ECONOMIC, AND ENERGY-FRIENDLY SOLUTION</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-28/</guid>
      <description>Bringing new and practical perspectives on energy efficiency, the Institute of Smart City and Management (UEH-ISCM) in collaboration with Yonsei University (Korea) Utrecht University and Potsdam University (Germany) cordially invite you to attend the Webinar “Maximizing Energy Efficiency: Sustainable Economic, and Energy-friendly Solution”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEN FOR REGISTRATION | UBU SUMMER COURSE: NIGHT ECONOMY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-20/</guid>
      <description>Are you someone who is daring, willing to learn and experience new things?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPENING UEH MAKERSPACE SPACE AND OPENING APPLICATION FOR WOOD LAMP WORKSHOP - THE MAKERS&#39; LAMP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-24/</guid>
      <description>LAUNCHING THE UEH MAKERSPACE AND OPEN FOR REGISTRATION FOR THE MAKERS’ LAMP WORKSHOP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A LOOK AT SEAUS INTERNATIONAL SCIENCE CONFERENCE 2023: URBAN DESIGN SOLUTIONS IN SOUTHEAST ASIA TO SOLVE GLOBAL Warming</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-25/</guid>
      <description>RECAP SEAUS 2023 International Scientific Conference: Urban Design Solutions In Southeast Asia Towards Solving The Problem Of Global Warming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPLORE: VUNG TAU COASTAL CITY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-37/</guid>
      <description>As a place where the chosen site challenges our talented competitors in the 3rd International Design Competition: Reimagining Cities towards Carbon Neutrality located, Vung Tau coastal city has its own prospects, which can be utilized in its process of developing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEN FOR REGISTRATION | FROM UNLEASH THE UNIQUENESS TO CONTRIBUTE POSITIVELY TO THE COMMUNITY WITH INTERNATIONAL PROJECT: ENHANCE QUALITY OF LIFE IN HCMC WITH ART AND DESIGN</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-26/</guid>
      <description>OPEN FOR REGISTRATION | FROM UNLEASH THE UNIQUENESS TO CONTRIBUTE POSITIVELY TO THE COMMUNITY WITH INTERNATIONAL PROJECT: ENHANCE QUALITY OF LIFE IN HCMC WITH ART AND DESIGN</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOIN US AT THE 1st REGIONAL CONFERENCE: SOUTH EAST ASIAN URBANISMS TO ADDRESS GLOBAL WARMING</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-19/</guid>
      <description>With rapid urban growth, shifts in productivity, and a rush toward modernization, there is a risk of homogenizing territories and settlement systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEAM UEH FESTIVAL - EXPERIENCE ROBOT ART AND TECHNOLOGY FOR FUTURE KIDS ON THE  OCCASION OF 1/6</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-21/</guid>
      <description>In order to welcome the International Children’s Day 01/06, UEH Trade Union, School of Media Design (SMD), Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM), Institute of Intelligent and Interactive Technologies (3I) organized an interesting artistic and technological activities, following the STEAM direction: Science, Technology, Engineering, Art and Mathematics for children of staffs and lecturers of UEH.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOIN THE BROWNFIELD REDEVELOPMENT WEBINAR: UNLOCKING URBAN SUSTAINABILITY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-18/</guid>
      <description>Join the Brownfield Redevelopment Webinar: Unlocking Urban Sustainability&#xA;Are you interested in unlocking the potential of brownfields to revitalize your community, create jobs, and protect the environment?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMART AND RESILIENT LANDSCAPE DESIGN EXHIBITION: LET’S SEE HOW UEH’S SPACE IS CHANGING</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-17/</guid>
      <description>This weekend, ISCM is hosting the Smart and Resilient Landscape Design Exhibition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEN FOR REGISTRATION | SEMINAR: BARRIER-FREE SMART CITY FOR PEOPLE WITH DISABILITIES</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-16/</guid>
      <description>A new direction in the Smart City developing process, A Barrier-free Smart City for People with Disabilities sets the target to ensure that citizens, especially people with disabilities, have the right to approach and use the utilities as well as services of the cities conveniently and easily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORKSHOP: THINKBIKE - SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-12/</guid>
      <description>To find an equitable answer to the true questions of sustainable urban mobility in the 21st century, the Consulate General of the Kingdom of the Netherlands in HCMC together with University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH) organize the ThinkBike Sustainable Development Workshop, with the participation of international experts from Dutch Cycling Embassy, ​​Humankind, Royal HaskoningDHV and UEH College of Technology and Design (CTD).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEN FOR REGISTRATION | LAUNCH EVENT - 3RD INTERNATIONAL DESIGN COMPETITION: REIMAGINING CITIES TOWARDS CARBON NEUTRALITY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-11/</guid>
      <description>Following urbanization, many urban problems happened. Climate change has negatively affected the whole world, and VietNam is one of the countries that has been greatly influenced by that negative climate phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEN FOR REGISTRATION | DEMO CLASS: FROM DREAM TO LIFE - BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURAL AND URBAN DESIGN INCLUSIVE SMART CITY PROGRAM</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-10/</guid>
      <description>OPEN FOR REGISTRATION | DEMO CLASS: FROM DREAM TO LIFE - BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURAL AND URBAN DESIGN INCLUSIVE SMART CITY PROGRAM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORKSHOP: URBAN SKETCH</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-05/</guid>
      <description>Mở đầu chuỗi sự kiện của năm 2023 - Design for Carbon Neutral Future, Viện Đô thị Thông minh và Quản lý (ISCM) phối hợp cùng Urban Sketchers Vietnam mang đến cơ hội được giao lưu, học tập thông qua việc trải nghiệm ký họa ngoài trời với Workshop Urban Sketch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASTER ORIENTATION DAY - A SPECIAL GREETING FOR THE MASTER OF SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-04/</guid>
      <description>MASTER ORIENTATION DAY - A SPECIAL GREETING FOR THE MASTER OF SMART CITY AND INNOVATION MANAGEMENT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK/Vietnam Season 2023 | D-FUSE workshop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2023-01/</guid>
      <description>On their visit to Vietnam following the scoping grant by the British Council, D-Fuse would like to give a talk about their work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORKSHOP: FIBONACCI BOX</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-49/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-49/</guid>
      <description>In order to improve geometric spatial thinking, make spatial proportions in architecture a habit, and apply them to the reality of the upcoming Christmas and New Year events, the Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM) is working with partners CASAtelier and N.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FR] [SPECIAL SESSION] SMART MOBILITY TOWARD SUSTAINABILITY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-47/</guid>
      <description>DATE &amp;amp; TIME: 09/12/2022 | 3:15 PM (UTC+7)&#xA;AVENUE: Room B1-205 | University of Economics HCMC, 279 Nguyễn Tri Phương, Ward 5, District 10, TP HCM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[R4N/FR] [SPECIAL SESSION] CITY 4.0 FOR FUTURE RESILIENCE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-48/</guid>
      <description>[FR/R4N] [SPECIAL SESSION] CITY 4.0 FOR FUTURE RESILIENCE: TECHNOLOGY AND FUTURE RESILIENCE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANNOUNCEMENT: THE EVENT SERIES READY FOR NEXT - FUTURE RESILIENCE THROUGH SMART CITY LENS IS HAPPENING</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-44/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-44/</guid>
      <description>Events Series “Ready for Next: Transforming for Sustainability” (R4N) organized by UEH in collaboration with other international partners from Dec 04 - 11, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FR] [SPECIAL SESSION] 15 MINUTES CITY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-46/</guid>
      <description>Can you picture yourselves living in a city where food, drinks and other necessities could be accessed in 15 minutes ?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Ready for Next - Special Session] METAVERSE: CITY OF TOMORROW</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-45/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-45/</guid>
      <description>2021 was the year of several difficulties and changes. In that picture, digital technologies have defined their own position and roles in economics and society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORKSHOP: SUSTAINABLE FASHION</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-14/</guid>
      <description>As we grow more aware of the significant influence that our clothing has on the environment, the term &amp;ldquo;sustainable fashion&amp;rdquo; is becoming more and more popular (and overused).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORIENTATION DAY K48 - READY FOR THE NEXT FUTURE!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-18/</guid>
      <description>Every year, the Institute of Smart City and Management will organize a special program - Orientation Day to welcome our new students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORKSHOP: GREEN BUILDING</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-19/</guid>
      <description>Buildings have extensive direct and indirect impacts on the environment. During their construction, occupancy, renovation, repurposing, and demolition, buildings use energy, water, and raw materials, generate waste, and emit potentially harmful atmospheric emissions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Workshop: Global City Development Camp - Orientation Day - The Beginning of Miracle Meeting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/international-workshop-global-city-development-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/international-workshop-global-city-development-camp/</guid>
      <description>About Event Now in Vinh Long city, going through a difficult time of Covid 19, the magical meeting between Korean and Vietnamese students officially occurred after more than a few months of preparation and waiting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seminar: 35 Years of Optical remote sensing in Geography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/seminar-35-years-of-optical-remote-sensing-in-geography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/seminar-35-years-of-optical-remote-sensing-in-geography/</guid>
      <description>OGIS (Geographic Information System) - is an effective tool and plays an important role in many defenses, and economic and political activities of various organizations and countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISCM &amp; KOREA TRIP: CONNECTING COOPERATION AND MORE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-06/</guid>
      <description>As part of a series of events to foster collaboration with universities around the world as part of the 2022 - A Future Resilience Through Smart City Lens event series, the Institute of Smart City and Management had a field trip from August 22-30 to experience, discuss cooperation with various smart city research agencies and units as well as universities in Korea, one of the leading countries in smart city development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seminar: 35 Years of Optical remote sensing in Geography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-seminar-35-years-of-optical-remote-sensing-in-geography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-seminar-35-years-of-optical-remote-sensing-in-geography/</guid>
      <description>OGIS (Geographic Information System) - is an effective tool and plays an important role in many defenses, and economic and political activities of various organizations and countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Workshop: Global City Development Camp - Orientation Day - The Beginning of Miracle Meeting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-international-workshop-global-city-development-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-international-workshop-global-city-development-camp/</guid>
      <description>About Event Now in Vinh Long city, going through a difficult time of Covid 19, the magical meeting between Korean and Vietnamese students officially occurred after more than a few months of preparation and waiting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FROM UEH HO CHI MINH CITY CAMPUS  TO UEH VINH LONG BRANCH - THE FIRST CAMPUS TRANSFER PROGRAM IN UEH FOR BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURAL AND URBAN DESIGN INCLUSIVE SMART CITY (BAUD)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-05/</guid>
      <description>In addition to studying in modern Studiolab, ISCM always strives to provide learners with the most practical experience to understand the industry and provide learners with multi-dimensional perspectives and ways of thinking, which encourages learners to continuously expand the framework of creativity, thinking, and vision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEBINAR : STORIES OF COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-10/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Time: 10 AM - 11.30 AM (GMT+7) | Ngày 8 tháng 6 năm 2022 🌟 Format: Online | Free of charge 🌟 Register link: https://bit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORKSHOP ART SUMMER CAMP FOR KIDS (ASCK)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-31/</guid>
      <description>OPEN REGISTRATION FOR WORKSHOP ART SUMMER CAMP FOR KIDS (ASCK)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL WORKSHOP: UNIVERSITY STUDENT LIFE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-35/</guid>
      <description>INTERNATIONAL WORKSHOP: UNIVERSITY STUDENT LIFE&#xA;—&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;&#xA;Time: 2PM - 3.30PM (UTC+ 7) - Sunday, March 27, 2022</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISCM experienced Porsche Sai Gon Showroom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-01-16_porsche/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2022-01-16_porsche/</guid>
      <description>On January 16, the ISCM team and students were honoured to represent UEH University to attend the Porsche Saigon experience in Ho Chi Minh City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartCity&#43; Festival &#43; Exhibition 2021</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-smartcity&#43;_exhibition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-smartcity&#43;_exhibition/</guid>
      <description>Time: from 8AM to 6PM - December 17, 2021</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartCity&#43; Festival 2021: Webinar: City for All &amp; City Branding and Sustainability</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-smartcity&#43;_webinar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-smartcity&#43;_webinar/</guid>
      <description>When urbanization occurs, we often encounter the choice of equity or efficiency for city development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartCity&#43; Festival 2021</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-smartcity&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-smartcity&#43;/</guid>
      <description>The year 2021 will be remembered for major changes in different areas, as well as an uncertain future due to Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bachelor Orientation Day-Dream right-Dream sao-cho đúng</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-ba-orientation-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-ba-orientation-day/</guid>
      <description>____________&#xA;In our dreams, between virtual and real, there is always a significant gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orientation Day - Master of Smart City and Innovation Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-masterorientation-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-masterorientation-day/</guid>
      <description>____________&#xA;The Institute of Smart Cities and Management (ISCM) is delighted to welcome the first generation of the Executive Master of Smart City and Innovation courses in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judging Panel Event - Slogan Competition “For The Multidisciplinary and Sustainable UEH University</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/slogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/slogan/</guid>
      <description>About Event After nearly a month of launching, the UEH Slogan competition received positive support from the domestic and international creative community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UEH Slogan Competition Invitation: for the Multi-disciplinary and Sustainable UEH University</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/khoi-dong-cuoc-thi-slogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/khoi-dong-cuoc-thi-slogan/</guid>
      <description>About Event In its 45 years of establishment and growth since 1976, the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City (UEH) has accumulated countless accolades from various reputable organizations across the world for its outstanding performance in teaching, research, and social contribution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Design Competition SmartCity&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-international-design-competition-smartcity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/2021-international-design-competition-smartcity/</guid>
      <description>About Event Following the great success of the 1st international online international design competition in 2019 with the theme &amp;ldquo;Future City: Smart design for the post-pandemic world&amp;rdquo;, the annual contest launched by the Institute of Smart Cities and Management in collaboration with nearly 20 partners will be held for the second time in 2021 with the theme &amp;ldquo;SMARTCITY+&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Webinar towards bldg. Resilient &amp; Sustainable Communities through Disaster Mitigation&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/international-webinar-toward-bldg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/international-webinar-toward-bldg/</guid>
      <description>About Event A webinar entitled &amp;ldquo;International webinar towards building resilient and sustainable communities through disaster mitigation&amp;rdquo; and co-hosted by the University of the Northern Philippines, the University of the Cordilleras, and Nueva Ecija University of Science and Technology will take place on August 27th and 28th.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admission Consulting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/tu-van-tuyen-sinh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/tu-van-tuyen-sinh/</guid>
      <description>About Event Choosing a major to follow is not easy for students and parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar &#34;Blockchain for DeFi &amp; Cryptocurrency - Blockchain in Current and Future Economy&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/webinar-blockchain-for-defi-cryptocurrency-blockchain-in-current-and-future-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/webinar-blockchain-for-defi-cryptocurrency-blockchain-in-current-and-future-economy/</guid>
      <description>About Event In the wave of the fourth industrial revolution, blockchain is regarded as the &amp;ldquo;key&amp;rdquo; technology for digital transformation and the development of the technological platform of the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Summer Design Camp 2021: Smart Design City for Zero Carbon Emission</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/international-summer-design-camp-2021-smart-design-city-for-zero-carbon-emission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/international-summer-design-camp-2021-smart-design-city-for-zero-carbon-emission/</guid>
      <description>About Event INTERNATIONAL SUMMER DESIGN CAMP 2021: Smart Design City for Zero Carbon Emission</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Urban Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/thi%E1%BA%BFt-k%E1%BA%BF-%C4%91%C3%B4-th%E1%BB%8B-t%E1%BA%A7m-nh%C3%ACn-v%E1%BB%AFng-ch%E1%BA%AFc-cho-%C4%91%C3%B4-th%E1%BB%8B-b%E1%BB%81n-v%E1%BB%AFng/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/thi%E1%BA%BFt-k%E1%BA%BF-%C4%91%C3%B4-th%E1%BB%8B-t%E1%BA%A7m-nh%C3%ACn-v%E1%BB%AFng-ch%E1%BA%AFc-cho-%C4%91%C3%B4-th%E1%BB%8B-b%E1%BB%81n-v%E1%BB%AFng/</guid>
      <description>About Event On March 25, in Ho Chi Minh City, the Institute of Smart Cities and Management, in cooperation with B+H, held a webinar with the theme &amp;ldquo;A new understanding of the imperative of healthy city design&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webinar “a New Understanding of the Imperative of Healthy City Design&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/webinar-a-new-understanding-of-the-imperative-of-healthy-city-design-official-starts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/webinar-a-new-understanding-of-the-imperative-of-healthy-city-design-official-starts/</guid>
      <description>About Event B+H, in partnership with Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM), are pleased to invite you to an engaging conservation focused on the “Future of healthy and sustainable urban development in Vietnam”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workshop and Webinar Week &#34;Staycation, the Hospitable City - Why Not?&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/workshop-and-webinar-international-week-staycation-the-hospitable-city-why-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/workshop-and-webinar-international-week-staycation-the-hospitable-city-why-not/</guid>
      <description>On March 1st, 2021, the opening ceremony of workshop week with the theme “Global Strategies for Local Tourism” was successfully organized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Line of SmartCity&#43; Arttech Fusion Program of ISCM Event Series 2021</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/on-the-line-of-smartcity-arttech-fusion-program-of-iscm-event-series-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/on-the-line-of-smartcity-arttech-fusion-program-of-iscm-event-series-2021/</guid>
      <description>About Event We would like to invite you to participate the webinar “Livable smart city: how to build up for the sustainable future city”, with our international and local experts and professors of Vietnam, America, Belgium and England.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Culture, Cohesion and Civic Society: How Smart Cities Build on the Best of Our Past?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/culture-cohesion-and-civic-society-how-smart-cities-build-on-the-best-of-our-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/culture-cohesion-and-civic-society-how-smart-cities-build-on-the-best-of-our-past/</guid>
      <description>About Event On December 21st, 2020, the webinar “Culture, Cohesion and Civic Society: How Smart Cities Build on the Best of Our Past?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UEH University hosted the Southeast Region of the National Festival for Innovative Startups – TechFest 2020</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/unviersity-of-economics-ho-chi-minh-city-hosted-the-southeast-region-of-the-national-festival-for-innovative-startups--techfest-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/unviersity-of-economics-ho-chi-minh-city-hosted-the-southeast-region-of-the-national-festival-for-innovative-startups--techfest-2020/</guid>
      <description>About Event On November 24, 2020, University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City hosted the Southeast Region of the national festival for innovative startups – TECHFEST 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Launch Event</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/international-launch-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 06:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/international-launch-event/</guid>
      <description>Institute of Smart City and Management (ISCM)-University of Economics HCMC (UEH) today has successfully organized an international launch event, along with the prize-giving ceremony for the 1st international design contest “Future city: design for the post-pandemic world”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Campus Planning toward Satellite City and College Town</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/smart-campus-planning-toward-satellite-city-college-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/smart-campus-planning-toward-satellite-city-college-town/</guid>
      <description>About Event As usual, in term of choosing institutions, students and their parents own a desire to be closer to their families while still wanting the best college education.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innovative Approach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/innovative-approach-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/innovative-approach-1/</guid>
      <description>To adapt to rapid-development and urbanization, what innovative and innovative approaches will be suitable to solve or eliminate urban issues toward smart cities development?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launch Event: BAUD - BAS Dual-Degree Program</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event/launch-event-baud-bas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event/launch-event-baud-bas/</guid>
      <description>About Event On September 3, 2021, the Institute of Smart City and Management of the University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City and the Faculty of Creative Arts and Industries of the University of Auckland successfully launched the Bachelor of Architecture and Urban Design (BAUD) and Bachelor of Architectural Studies (BAS) dual-degree programs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
